My name's Harrison. I own a landscaping business, so one of my guys actually
backed into my girlfriend's Jeep.
Ooh.
Yeah, I know. And so I brought it here thinking I'm going to be paying a
lot of money, and actually it was a lot less than I thought.
And the time that they said it was going to be done, a couple of weeks or whatever,
it was less than that, and honestly, it looked better than it did from
factory. So just a great experience. Great guys.
And I got some work out of it for my landscaping business, so it's a win-win for
everybody.
You got work out of it?
Yeah. I do the snow here, plow the snow.
Oh, okay.
So it's a win-win for everybody.
Yeah. So, what kind of Jeep?
Jeep Wrangler 2020\. Yep.
Uh-oh.
I know.
And one of your guys backed into hers.
With a trailer, yeah.
So you had to cover it.
Yeah.
Was she happy with the work?
Oh, she loved it. Yeah, she was very excited.
Yeah. So is this like the first kind of accident you had to deal with?
Yeah. First accident.
Okay.
Now, look, anytime something happens, I'll always come here. Great guys.
Absolutely great guys.